翻译：陈继民
在我们开始之前
让我们创建一个项目，添加一些引用
然后集中我们的时候
用来设计我们的应用
我们要采用一些稍微有些不同的布局方式
相比我们之前课程所用到的
可能会用到一些不同的新技术
不说其他的了，让我先把摄像头关了
以便我能集中注意力
我们要创建一个新的项目
把它命名为UWPSoundBoard.
然后像往常一样
删掉整个帧数计数器
然后我要做的是添加一些引用
这里有几种不一样的引用
对于这个项目，你可以下载这些
从之前的视频或者当前的视频
在那些视频下面有下载链接
回过头来，你会发现这里存在着一些模式
这里这些全部都是音频
然后这些icon图标文件与这些wav音频文件相对应
所以每个子文件夹都有两个这样的wav音频文件
如果我们回到image文件夹，这里也是一样的
只不过这里是png而不是wav文件
下一个类型的文件夹里面是我们的图标文件
这些会用在分割视图里的窗格里
我们通常用来显示一系列的选项
每个都代表着不同种类的东西
最后，这里有一个PackageAppXManifest文件夹
还有这些logo图标
用于启动画面的图标
这些东西会被要求提供
当我们准备把这个app提交的应用商店的时候
但是不凑巧的是，你把这些东西复制进去的办法
并不是那么简单
你会发现这里会有一些奇怪的地方
Audio有一个子文件夹，然后里面会有相应的文件
所以当你拖拽这个文件夹
到你的引用文件夹里，你会发现
里面并没有子文件夹！
然而它本来应该有的！
所以我想我们并没有把他们复制进去
所以你需要进到子文件里，然后拖拽它们到vs里
然后vs会提示！它们已经存在？！（萌叔魔性笑声）
就像这样
只需要点击“应用于所有项”
然后就好了~
所以我们应该有四个文件夹
然后再Audio子文件夹里每一个子文件应该有两个音频文件
用同样的方法处理Icon文件夹
拖拽大法好！
什么都没有~
只是我们把它们添加到当前的项目里
所以全选它们，拖拽进去~
你确定吗？已经存在这些文件里！不，并没有（萌叔吐槽时间）
再次添加，然后用同样的办法处理Image文件夹
对于每个音频文件
没有子文件夹，但是我们知道它们在那
拖拽大法！
你确定吗？？？是的！
然后就好了
最后到PackageAppXManifest文件夹
完成这最后的一小块工作
这样就完成了！
稍后我们会用到它们
全屏一下~
把引用文件夹关闭，打开MainPage.xaml
所以这次我打算采用一种稍微不同的布局方式
我们会有一个网格布局
它会提供最上面的一行
里面包含了一个相对布局
包含一个汉堡菜单按钮，后退按钮和一个..
大概是一个自动建议列表
然后再第二行，我们会放置一个分割布局
开始干活吧！
打码打码打码Grid.RowDefinitions.
RowDefinition Height="Auto".
我们已经做过这一步很多次了
所以这一步应该不是那么难
然后放置一个相对布局
里面包含顶部的对象
再下面放置一个分割布局
里面包含其他的主体对象
在相对布局里，我打算放置
首先，是一个汉堡菜单按钮
然后添加一个后退按钮
然后是一个自动建议列表
RelativePanel.AlignRightWithPanel = "True".
添加一个名字
给汉堡菜单按钮
后退按钮应该设置为 RelativePanel.AlignLeftWith...
抱歉！, 应该是RelativePanel.Rightof=“HamburgerButton”.
汉堡菜单按钮应该是RelativePanelAlignLeftWithPanel.
That should be pretty much self-evident,
but I'll put it there anyway.
I'm going to add a Click Event here
because I know I'm going to need it.
Go ahead and space these guys out.
I also know I'm going to need to put
for example, FontFamily is going to be Segoe MDL2 Assets
and then the Content will be, let's see if I remember,
"&xE700;"
If I got that right from memory,
I will be impressed with myself.
Which just goes to show, I don't memorize this.
Most people don't memorize these obscure little things.
That's why you have a cheat sheet.
Or you have the cheat sheet called the Internet
you can always reference.
Yep, I got it right. Wow, I'm impressed.
With myself. (laughs)
It's the little things, right?
Okay, so next up I need a name for this Button
so let's give it the name of BackButton.
That's necessary because I'm going to give it the
Click equals NewEventHandler.
Here again, I want FontFamily equals Segoe MDL2 Assets.
And then Content="&#xE"... something or other.
You know I got to the point where I decided
I'm going to put the Character Map right here
on my task bar. And I think this is the one I want.
There's a bunch of these back arrows that have various uses.
But I'll use this one, 0A6.
That should be sufficient. 0A6.
And then the AutoSuggestBox,
there's really not much I need to do here,
I would need to give it a Name though.
So let's give it the name of search AutoSuggestBox.
And I'm going to put PlaceholderText equal to
to "Search for sounds".
I know I want the Width to be 200
from that previous exercise that we did together.
And I know the QueryIcon I want defined QueryIcon.
Then I know that I'm going to handle the TextChanged Event
because we're going to filter the list based on that.
I also know that I want the QuerySubmitted Event
to handle that one as well.
Everything else though, I'm going to leave for now.
We'll come back to that in a while
when we try to actually get that functionality working.
Let's see now, that's the RelativePanel.
Now we haven't touched the SplitView yet
so let's see what we have first before we move on here.
See if there's anything glaringly wrong
with anything I've done up to this point.
These look awfully small, I'll probably change the Height
and the Width of Buttons themselves
and then change the Font.
So I'm going to use Height and Width of 45
like we did in the previous exercise for these Buttons.
So Height="45", Width="45"
I like that, that feels good to me.
And then also I want to set the FontSize="20".
Alright, so that should be good enough for now
with that RelativePanel area.
Okay great. Need some padding,
but we'll come back for that later.
Alright next up, SplitView. Let's give it a name
because we're going to have to reference it programatically.
So MySplitView, DisplayMode,
I know I want that to be CompactOverlay,
I also know that I want the CompactPaneLength equal
to be 45, that would be the Width of the buttons
that I have above it, so I like that.
Then the OpenPaneLength, I don't know, 150 should be fine
but let me just put 200 here.
I seem to remember it's going to be a little bit larger
for some reason
having gone through this once already.
So that's good, so we got that.
And now inside of this I need the SplitView.Pane
and I then need the SplitView.Content.
In the Pane, we're going to have a ListBox
like we've always had, or actually, I'm sorry.
I'm going to do things a little bit different this time.
I'll use a ListView this time.
I'm going to Bind to the items and just use Data Binding
and Bind to a List that I'll create in the code behind
for the MainPage.xaml.
I guess I will work on that in this lesson.
Anyway, I know that we want the is ItemClickEnabled
equal true on this, I know I'm going
to handle the ItemClick event on this as well.
Probably should give it a name. Bummer.
So Name="MenuItemsListView".
And so, let me regenerate that.
And I know I need a Template, and I know I need a Source.
I'll come back to that in a minute.
Now, in this area, I'm actually going to add,
in the Content area I'm going to add a Grid
because I'm going to actually split this into two Rows.
There will be a top Row that'll contain
what's being displayed in the main area
and then below that I'll have the items
that will be displayed.
So I'm going to need some RowDefinitions.
So RowDefinitionHeight="Auto".
So I know, whoops, let's not get here in the wrong spot.
Okay, there we go.
In this top Row I'm going to add a StackPanel
and it's just going to contain TextBlock.
I don't even know that I need the StackPanel, honestly.
I could probably do without it, in fact,
I will do without it. Just get rid of it.
Let's just go straight with the TextBlock.
And we'll set Name="CategoryTextBlock".
Text="All Sounds".
That will be the default text in there.
I'm going to make this kind of like a header,
so we'll set the FontSize="24".
Okay. And then in the lower area I'll add the GridView
beneath that and that'll contain all of our items.
And we'll set that Grid.Row="1".
And I'll call this Name="SoundGridView".
Alright, this is really the key one we want to focus on.
We want to set the SelectionMode="None".
All I want someone to be able to do is click on a sound
and it play the sound, I don't need selection.
I do want to set the is ItemClickEnabled that goes true
because I do want it to be clickable.
So then the ItemClick Event should be handled.
Now I know I'm going to need an Item Source
and all that business and I'll come back to that.
So let's go GridView.ItemTemplate
and then set the DataTemplate
and then let's put an Image inside of there.
And I happen to know that the Height
and the Widths are kind of weird
because when gave the specifications
to the guy who was working on it,
I just gave some arbitrary number
based on a mock-up that I'd created.
As I look at my notes here, I see is it 101 Width.
And we'll have to set the Source on that as well,
we'll come back to that later
whenever we do the Data Binding
in the next lesson.
But there's one other interesting little thing
that I want to stick here as well in this area.
And that is the MediaElement.
The media element allows you to play sounds
and we'll become very familiar
with that two videos from now.
Let me go ahead and give it the Name MyMediaElement.
And I'm going to set a property called AutoPlay="True".
And that just says, whenever I give you a Source,
so Assets/Sounds/Cow, whatever,
just go ahead and play it,
I'm not going to programatically tell you
to start and stop playing, just play, auto play.
Alright, I think that's all that I'm going to do here
in this first video. We covered a lot of ground.
There's a lot left to do.
But we'll come back and get them
on subsequent passes at this.
So at this point there's really not a lot to this app,
it's just kind of the shell
and we'll come back and we'll fill in a lot of this stuff.
Okay, pick it up in the next lesson, thanks.